soulspottv.com 2018-06-29

# Privacy Policy | SOULSpot

Scroll down to read more about how SOULSpot respects your privacy

Privacy Policy for http://soulspottv.com

The privacy of our visitors to http://soulspottv.com is important to us.

At http://soulspottv.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit http://soulspottv.com, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.  
**We collect but do not link personal and activity data.  
**We use technologies like cookies (small files stored by your browser), web beacons, or unique device identifiers to anonymously identify your computer or device so we can deliver a better experience. Our systems also log information like your browser, operating system and IP address.

We also may collect personally identifiable information that you provide to us, such as your name, address, phone number or email address. With your permission, we may also access other personal information on your device, such as your phone book, calendar or messages, in order to provide services to you. If authorized by you, we may also access profile and other information from services like Facebook.

Our systems are not designed to associate personal information with your activities (such as pages you view or things you click on or search for).

We do not knowingly contact or collect personal information from children under 13. If you believe we have inadvertently collected such information, please contact us so we can promptly obtain parental consent or remove the information.

Our service does not currently recognize the “Do Not Track” signal that may be available in some web browsers.

We also use third party advertisements on http://soulspottv.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

We Log Files  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

 **We do not store or share your precise location.**

We do not use or collect your precise geographic location. 

 **You can request to see your personal data.**

You can sign into your account to see any personally identifiable information we have stored, such as your name, email, address or phone number. You can also contact us by email to request to see this information. 

 **We keep personal data until you delete it.**

We remove personally identifiable information (such as your name, address, email or phone number) and other preferences associated with your account promptly after you delete your account. We may retain other data indefinitely. 

 **We don’t share your personal data with other companies.  
**We generally do not share personally identifiable information (such as name, address, email or phone) with other companies. 

 **Ad companies collect anonymous data. You can opt out.  
**Ad companies may use and collect anonymous data about your interests to customize content and advertising here and in other sites and applications. Interest and location data may be linked to your device, but is not linked to your identity. Click to see company privacy policies and opt-out choices: 

Google (www.google.com) operates the Google Display Network (comprising partner websites and some Google properties like YouTube), DoubleClick online ad serving products and the DoubleClick Ad Exchange, and Invite Media. These provide advertisers with the tools needed to plan, execute and analyze marketing programs with greater ease and efficiency, while enabling publishers to maximize their returns from online advertising. Note: Because Google uses DoubleClick and Invite technology, cookies placed by Google for behavioral advertising, including the opt out cookie, will appear as DoubleClick and Invite cookies.   

 [Google Ads (Admeld, Admob, Channel Intelligence, DoubleClick, Display Network, Teracent)](http://www.privacychoice.org/policy/text?policy=db5e6fe8f7a730ced164644365d4da9e#) 

Admeld Admeld pioneered the private ad exchange and built technology that made it easy for publishers to identify new opportunities and control how every impression is sold. Admob AdMob has been rebuilt, leveraging the best of Google’s ad platforms. Channel Intelligence Channel intelligence optimizes product visibility on shopping engines. With our bidding expertise, data optimization technology, and data quality monitoring, we elevate performance on shopping engines. DoubleClick DoubleClick for Publishers (DFP) is a comprehensive hosted ad serving platform that streamlines ad management functions and allows generating even-greater advertising margins. Display Network The Google Display Network helps generate awareness by getting ads in front of consumers, so they can learn about the business as they consider their options. Teracent Teracent’s Intelligent Display Advertising creates display ads entirely customized to the specific consumer and site proposition for marketers that was, until now, cost and time prohibitive.   

DoubleClick DART cookies  
We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (“interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting <http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx>

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

**You can ask privacy questions.  
**If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policies, please contact us:  
[[Contact us](http://soulspottv.com/contact-us/)] OR [EMAIL]

 **Analytics providers access data on our behalf.  
**Analytics companies may access anonymous data (such as your IP address or device ID) to help us understand how our services are used. They use this data solely on our behalf. They do not share it except in aggregate form; no data is shared as to any individual user. Click to see company privacy policies that govern their use of data. 

 [Google Ads (Admeld, Admob, Channel Intelligence, DoubleClick, Display Network, Teracent)](http://www.privacychoice.org/policy/text?policy=db5e6fe8f7a730ced164644365d4da9e#) 

Admeld Admeld pioneered the private ad exchange and built technology that made it easy for publishers to identify new opportunities and control how every impression is sold. Admob AdMob has been rebuilt, leveraging the best of Google’s ad platforms. Channel Intelligence Channel intelligence optimizes product visibility on shopping engines. With our bidding expertise, data optimization technology, and data quality monitoring, we elevate performance on shopping engines. DoubleClick DoubleClick for Publishers (DFP) is a comprehensive hosted ad serving platform that streamlines ad management functions and allows generating even-greater advertising margins. Display Network The Google Display Network helps generate awareness by getting ads in front of consumers, so they can learn about the business as they consider their options. Teracent Teracent’s Intelligent Display Advertising creates display ads entirely customized to the specific consumer and site proposition for marketers that was, until now, cost and time prohibitive.   

Google Analytics is a web analytics tool that helps website owners understand how visitors engage with their website. Google Analytics customers can view a variety of reports about how visitors interact with their website so they can improve it. Google Analytics collects information anonymously. It reports website trends without identifying individual visitors.   

 **We take steps to protect personal information  
**We take reasonable steps to secure your personally identifiable information against unauthorized access or disclosure. We encrypt transmission of data on pages where you provide payment information. However, no security or encryption method can be guaranteed to protect information from hackers or human error.

Information we collect may be stored or processed on computers located in any country where we do business. 

 **Special situations may require disclosure of your data.  
**To operate the service, we also may make identifiable and anonymous information available to third parties in these limited circumstances: (1) with your express consent, (2) when we have a good faith belief it is required by law, (3) when we have a good faith belief it is necessary to protect our rights or property, or (4) to any successor or purchaser in a merger, acquisition, liquidation, dissolution or sale of assets. Your consent will not be required for disclosure in these cases, but we will attempt to notify you, to the extent permitted by law to do so. 

 **You can review more privacy-related information.  
**This privacy policy was last updated on [August 2014]. Our privacy policy may change from time to time. If we make any material changes to our policies, we will place a prominent notice on our website or application. If the change materially affects registered users, we will send a notice to you by email, push notification or text.
